<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fit It</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="amit_shah">Amit Shah</string>
    <string name="bio">Bio</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="_9129784378">+9129784378</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="myntra_gmail_com">myntra@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>

    <!--    boby measurement text-->
    <string name="measurement_point1">1. Chest/Bust - Measure around the fullest part of the chest/bust. Do not draw the tape too tightly.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point2">2. Center Back Neck–to-Wrist- With arm straight, measure from back base of neck, across shoulder, and along arm to wrist.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point3">3. Back Waist Length- Measure from the most prominent bone at base of neck to the natural waistline.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point4">4. Cross Back- Measure from shoulder to shoulder.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point5">5. Arm Length- With arm slightly bent, measure from armpit to wrist.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point6">6. Upper Arm- Measure around the widest section of the upper arm located above the elbow.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point7">7. Armhole Depth- Measure from the top outside edge of the shoulder down to the armpit.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point8">8. Waist- Measure your waist at the smaller circumference of your natural waist, usually just above the belly button.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point9">9. Hip- Measure at the widest part of your lower hip.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point10">10. Head Circumference- For an accurate head measure, place a tape measure across the forehead and measure around the full circumference of the head. Keep the tape snug for accurate results.</string>
    <string name="measurement_point11">11. Sock Measurements- The following measurements are for crew-style or dress socks, which usually come several inches above the ankle and below the calf.</string>
    <string name="company_name">jfhvkjv</string>
    <string name="size">Size</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="my_homepage">My Homepage</string>
    <string name="_6_items">6 Items</string>

    <string name="t_shirt">T-Shirt</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
</resources>